[
    {
        "question": "What command do you use to commit using git?",
        "answer": "Git commit",
        "topic": "Git",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a popular package manager used for a mac?",
        "answer": " Homebrew",
        "topic": "General",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the linux command ls do?",
        "answer": "List files in current directory",
        "topic": "Linux",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What OS is chocolatey used on??",
        "answer": "Windows",
        "topic": "General",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What does mkdir do as a linux command?",
        "answer": "Make a directory",
        "topic": "Git",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a docker container?",
        "answer": "A isolated enviroment for running an app",
        "topic": "General",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "How would you check your node version?",
        "answer": "node -v",
        "topic": "Node",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "question": "What is docker?",
        "answer": "A platform for building running and shipping containers",
        "topic": "Docker",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "`Does linux use forward slashes or back slashes?",
        "answer": "Forward",
        "topic": "Linux",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does CD linux command do?",
        "Answer": "Change directory",
        "topic": "Linux",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "What GIT command would you use to create a directory?",
        "Answer": "Git init",
        "topic": "Git",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is GIT??",
        "Answer": "A version control system",
        "topic": "Git",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is kubernetes used for?",
        "Answer": "Application deployment",
        "topic": "Kubernetes",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the fastest way to find anything on a MAC?",
        "Answer": "command + space",
        "topic": "General",
        "asked": false
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is NPM?",
        "Answer": "Node package manager",
        "topic": "Node",
        "asked": false
    }
]
